<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Season6 on Adventure Time!</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/season6/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Season6 on Adventure Time!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/season6/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Food Chain (Season 6)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2014/06/season-6-food-chain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2014/06/season-6-food-chain/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The episode begins with candy children that have bodies resembling different shapes sliding down a slide, shouting with excitement. The kids are viewed from an horizontal angle in the next scene as they go through a playground-like structure. Finn and Jake are examining the &amp;lsquo;Catapilla Family&amp;rsquo;. After watching Princess Bubblegum teach the children about the Food Chain, they head to the snack bar as Finn found Princess Bubblegum&amp;rsquo;s class useless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While they&amp;rsquo;re walking Magic Man appears behind the two without them knowing, and transforms them into birds. After singing an electronic version of &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Der_H%C3%B6lle_Rache_kocht_in_meinem_Herzen&#34;&gt;Der Hölle Rache kocht in meinem Herzen&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;rdquo; they fly down below to a place with an oasis on it. Jake eats some caterpillars, which disgusts Finn. After that Finn tries eating the caterpillars and pukes on the ground. In the next scene, Finn and Jake are shown to be very chubby and sitting on the ground lazily. Finn becomes confused for why he became full from eating few caterpillars. Jake informs him that they have been eating for hours. Soon, Finn and Jake notice a shadow on the ground that gradually becomes bigger. They look up to see a big bird trying to attack them. Finn and Jake dodge this attack and attempt to fly away. However, because of Finn&amp;rsquo;s chubby body, Finn is not able to fly and skids across the ground. As the big bird flies closer, Finn cowers. The big bird does not recognize Finn and flies onward. As Finn tries to fly away, the big bird notices and flies towards him once again. Just as the big bird was close enough to strike, Magic Man converts Finn into the big bird.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finn then flies next to Jake. Jake does not recognize him, stating him as big and old. Finn hallucinates Jake as meat. Finn drools awfully, and states that Jake looks awesome and tasty. Finn asks Jake if he wants to go inside his mouth. Jake accepts and sits in his mouth. He states that Finn has a lot of saliva. Finn tries to eat Jake before he could escape from Finn&amp;rsquo;s mouth. Finn attempts again to eat him. Finn elevates lower until he hits the ground. He lays on the ground while the sun sets, stating how hungry he is, and dies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Finn is turned into hundreds of bacteria. The bacteria notices the dead body of the big bird as food and eats it. Jake is also turned into a bacterium and states that Finn eating the big bird is disgusting. The bacteria becomes full after the big bird results as a skeleton. The bacteria is then swept away by a gust of wind. Finn and Jake then find themselves turned into flowers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finn and Jake sing &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/We%27re_Plants&#34;&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re Plants&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;rdquo; during the song, caterpillars eat Finn and Jake&amp;rsquo;s leaves. Small birds come to eat the caterpillars. Finn and Jake are then turned into caterpillars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finn and Jake spot &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Erin&#34;&gt;Erin&lt;/a&gt; who faints from the heat. Finn crawls to Erin quickly, madly in love with her. Finn and Jake crawl with her in search of an oasis. Erin faints again, and Jake finds an oasis. Finn, Erin, and Jake eat the leaves in the oasis. After a short discussion, Erin and Finn decide to get married.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The scene changes into a leaf with a group of caterpillars with Jake hosting the marriage. Finn agrees to the marriage and everyone cheers. Suddenly, two birds are shown flying to the leaf, eating the caterpillars. Finn and Jake then changes into the birds eating the caterpillars until Finn was back into reality. Finn had caterpillars stuffed in his mouth in which he spitted them out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back into the reality, Finn realizes the lesson of the Food Chain and sings &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Food_Chain_(song&#34;&gt;Food Chain&lt;/a&gt;)&amp;ldquo;, which PB soon joins singing with him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The end shows Finn transforming into a bird-caterpillar-plant-bacteria hybrid while the kids leave due to boredom, once again entering the slide seen in the beginning.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breezy (Season 6)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2014/06/season-6-breezy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2014/06/season-6-breezy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The episode begins with &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Doctor_Princess&#34;&gt;Doctor Princess&lt;/a&gt; examining Finn&amp;rsquo;s flower arm, which is seen dull and has wilted some petals. He said that he had been drinking pickle juice a lot, but Doctor Princess told him to switch back to water. After this, she asks him how is he feeling, to which he replies he doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel anything and slumps out of the bed. Doctor Princess tells that that&amp;rsquo;s the reason and also that because his dad took his arm, his flower is starting to wilt and he is falling into depression. She tells him to have fun for the flower to continue its good growth, and Finn tells that she should come with him to &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Crab_Princess&#34;&gt;Crab Princess&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rsquo; party, to which she confusedly asks as a date. Finn replies yes, but she denies him, telling she doesn&amp;rsquo;t date her patients. Finn then walks out of the hospital.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The scene changes to a forest in which Finn was passing while slumping his body. While he was walking, he started to sing &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Lost_in_the_Darkness/Love&#34;&gt;Lost in the Darkness/Love&lt;/a&gt;, and while he was singing, a bee sees his flower and is attracted to it. The bee follows Finn to the party, where it is shown many princesses have arrived. Princess Bubblegum hosts as the DJ and all the others at the party start to dance while Finn sits on a near log with &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Raggedy_Princess&#34;&gt;Raggedy Princess&lt;/a&gt;. She asks Finn to help her pour juice from her cup into her mouth, as she couldn&amp;rsquo;t do it. Finn didn&amp;rsquo;t answer back as the bee annoys him by buzzing near his face. She tells him she can&amp;rsquo;t drink it, and asks his help. Finn is getting annoyed by the bee, as it constantly gets near to him and buzzes near his face. He tells the bee to cut it out, to which the bee apologizes, and says that she didn&amp;rsquo;t realize that the flower was attached to Finn&amp;rsquo;s arm. The bee says that the flower on Finn&amp;rsquo;s arm is the greatest miracle and she is completely attracted to it. Finn thanks her, and the bee introduces herself as &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Breezy_(character&#34;&gt;Breezy&lt;/a&gt;). Raggedy Princess somehow got the juice all over her face and went out to dance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Breezy wants the flower, so she gets very nervous. She asks Finn why he is there, to which he replies that he is there to make out with Crab Princess. Since Breezy is into the flower, she agrees to help Finn with his plans. Breezy sneaks near Crab Princess and hears that she wanted someone who could dance well. Breezy tells Finn, and he starts to dance and all princesses applaud his act. Crab Princess blushes as the scene changes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is seen that Finn eventually took her home, and drops her. She thanks Finn for walking her home, and Finn finally asks Crab Princess to get a kiss. She agrees and both of them kiss. Finn then bids her goodnight, to which Crab Princess replies happily and goes back to her home. Breezy congratulates Finn on his success. She then asks him how he feels, to which he says he is good, but cannot feel anything. He concludes if he made out with lots of girls, maybe he would feel something. Breezy gets near the flower, and seeing that it is good shape. Finn appreciates her help, and tells that she is a good wingman. Breezy appreciates this, and says she will help Finn to get more make outs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The scene changes to Breezy and Finn going to the &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Lizard_Kingdom&#34;&gt;Lizard Kingdom&lt;/a&gt;. They spy on &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Lizard_Princess&#34;&gt;Lizard Princess&lt;/a&gt; and Breezy whispers something to Finn and suddenly pushes him to go make out with her. Finn goes near Lizard Princess and takes the trumpet she was blowing. He plays good music that Lizard Princess is impressed by, and they kiss. Then everyone starts to dance as Finn plays the trumpet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The scene changes to now &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Muscle_Princess&#34;&gt;Muscle Princess&lt;/a&gt; dancing with Finn. Breezy tries to go near Finn&amp;rsquo;s flower, but since he is dancing and moving his arm, she doesn&amp;rsquo;t get a hold. Breezy notices that Muscle Princess is sweating, so she gives Finn a towel to help Muscle Princess wipe it off. Finn wipes it off and they then kiss each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The scene changes to &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Jake&#34;&gt;Jake&lt;/a&gt; skateboarding near the &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Tree_Fort&#34;&gt;Tree Fort&lt;/a&gt; where there are many ladies in wait. He goes inside to see Finn with a princess. She introduces herself as &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Frozen_Yogurt_Princess&#34;&gt;Frozen Yogurt Princess&lt;/a&gt;. Jake then says she is looking like somewhat a mix between &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Princess_Bubblegum&#34;&gt;Princess Bubblegum&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Flame_Princess&#34;&gt;Flame Princess&lt;/a&gt;, and so Jake teases Finn that he isn&amp;rsquo;t over with both of them. Finn gets angry and leaves with Breezy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finn tells Breezy, that he is just having fun, which is the doctor&amp;rsquo;s order. He also says but this isn&amp;rsquo;t helping him, and he should let the flower die. Breezy tells Finn that he has a responsibility to the flower. She also says she has responsibilities, as she was born as a virgin Queen Bee. She said that once she drinks the Royal Jelly, she will not be free as she is now. Finn tells her to stay free always, to which she agrees. She gets excited and suddenly she says that they should make out with each other, hinting she is attracted to him. Finn then gets confused while Breezy tries to cover up what she says.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As they run by a river, she faked an accident into bumping Finn to get hold of the flower, but they both fall in the river. As Finn floats on the river with Breezy atop, a male bee sees her and tells her to get back to her hive. She refuses and tells she has a carefree life and Finn agrees. Suddenly the bee calls more of his friends to deal with Finn. Finn starts to get attacked by them and fights them back but in vain. Breezy then goes to the hive of the male bees and comes back with a bottle of Royal Jelly. She tells him to not worry and she drinks the Royal Jelly. Breezy starts to transform in more humanoid type and bigger than Finn. She can now control the male bees and throws them back to their house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Breezy then tells she has become a Queen to save Finn, and also admits that she only wanted to help because she was attracted to the flower. She confesses that after hanging out with Finn, she loves him. She then tells Finn that he can partake at her pollen crumbles and become her drone. Finn appreciates this but tells Breezy that he wants to keep their relationship simple, and so Breezy gets hurt. She flies away while crying. The scene changes to Finn being with LSP and dancing. She tells him to stop dancing and to start making out. They both kiss, and Finn starts to go. To Finn one kiss is making out, but for LSP that&amp;rsquo;s not enough. She stops Finn and they make out LSP style.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The scene changes to Finn lying down. Finn then asks his flower arm if it was okay. It wilts, so he sends his memory of the &amp;ldquo;LSP make-out&amp;rdquo; into his mental vault.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are many fireflies flying and suddenly, the shadow of Breezy appears. She starts to sing, which helps the flower. Finn starts to sing with her unconsciously. When Finn notices Breezy, he sees her as Princess Bubblegum, holding a sword (which would later become known as the &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Finn_Sword&#34;&gt;Finn Sword&lt;/a&gt;). As soon as Breezy finishes the song, Finn&amp;rsquo;s flower arm grows into a great flowering tree and breaks. After ripping the remaining bark off, Finn sees a new arm covered in honey, with a thorn in it. Finn flicks the honey off to see that his original arm has grown back, and he starts to dance in joy. LSP wakes up to see Finn has gotten his arm back, and she was happy for him. Finn notices Breezy and his flower falling on her head. The episode ends with Breezy kissing the flower.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sad Face (Season 6)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2014/05/season-6-sad-face/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2014/05/season-6-sad-face/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The episode begins with &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Neptr&#34;&gt;Neptr&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/BMO&#34;&gt;BMO&lt;/a&gt; spying on a sleeping Finn and Jake. Neptr asks BMO what is going to happen and asks the cause of their spying to which BMO tells him to just watch, as this happens once in a month and also promises it would happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The scene changes to Jake and suddenly, his tail starts to wiggle. BMO points out this is what he called Neptr for, and they observe as Jake&amp;rsquo;s tail starts to move. Neptr is fascinated by it, and they follow Jake&amp;rsquo;s tail and spy on it. They sneak with the tail in the living room, and find that the tail has got a hat on his head. It further moves to get a cloth and packs some berries in it, and goes out of the treehouse. Neptr asks that where does the tail go, to which BMO replies it is none of their business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tail passes under a horse and through a bush to reach a tiny circus. The &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Ringmaster&#34;&gt;Ringmaster&lt;/a&gt; notices him, and refers to him as Blue Nose, hinting the tail must have worked for quite a time. He tells Blue Nose that he is late, and tells him to put on his makeup. Blue Nose obeys him and goes to a makeup room. The scene changes to inside the circus, where a blind grasshopper is throwing knives at a target at which another ant is tied on. The crowd is fascinated as a knife pierces the target just near the ant. Blue Nose is shown in the makeup room applying a white substance at the lower end, and painting a &amp;lsquo;blue nose&amp;rsquo;, and a sad face.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The scene again is changed at the circus and this time, the waving &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Snail&#34;&gt;Snail&lt;/a&gt; is performing a jump in a water pot, in which it succeeded and the crowd cheers. The snail exits, and a poor quality music starts playing. Blue Nose enters the arena with a cart of oranges and shows an act of taking an orange and rolling it in ground. The crowd observes it without any expression. Blue Nose finds a puppet bee in the cart, and wakes it up. It wakes up, and Blue Nose puts him on the ground. They both dance for a moment, then suddenly the bee dies and is taken off stage. Due to this boring act, the crowd criticizes Blue Nose, however, there is one little ant which is seen touched by the act and crying, although nobody notices her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The crowd throws various things at Blue Nose for an unimpressive act and Blue Nose exits from the arena. The Ringmaster is also bored by it and further criticizes Blue Nose. The Ringmaster then enters and announces an upcoming of a fierce performance and says it is about a dangerous beast in captivity. He announces the appearance of a chipmunk named Goralina, who is led by six ants and is in chains. They take Goralina on a raised platform and make it sit there. Blue Nose starts to see this, and sees the Ringmaster cruelly beating the chipmunk to perform for him. An audience throws an empty bottle of bug milk on its eye, to which she becomes enraged and breaks out of the chains and starts attacking the Ringmaster. She takes almost all of the crowd in its mouth. Blue Nose comes with a movable staircase and reaches near Goralina. He starts to hypnotize the chipmunk and succeeds. The grasshopper from an earlier act comes and throws the knife at Goralina. The chipmunk gets hypnotized and throws out the crowd she engulfed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The scene then fades out to the place of the Ringmaster. He is seen trying to put a 5 cent coin in a small box. Blue Nose approaches and the Ringmaster welcomes him. He talks about the show going completely wrong. He says that Goralina had given him a good amount of money the last show and is disappointed that no one rivaled Goralina today. He says there is another show in an hour and says to come up with an interesting act that will rival to the performance of her. Blue Nose is saddened by the fact that the chipmunk is kept there without her will, and goes to the cage of Goralina. He sees a sign indicating not to feed the monster. He rips it off and offers the berries he bought which she eats. Then he thinks about his next show and goes to his equipment chest. He sees a whoopee cushion and takes it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The scene fades to the arena and shows Blue Nose entering. He starts his same song used in the last show, and the Ringmaster thinks he will still perform the same bad act. Blue Nose instead goes to the middle, where there is a chair with a cushion on it. As soon as he sat on the cushion, it made a farting sound, to which the crowd laughed. The Ringmaster is awestruck and sees as the act continues. Blue Nose takes the whoopee cushion and throws it, and then proceeds to sit, but the chair breaks and the crowd laughs. He then goes to fill his water tumbler, but the water container throws water at his face. He starts to wrestle with it, but it kept throwing out water and the crowd laughed at it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He then proceeds to change his music to more hip type, but the record player doesn&amp;rsquo;t do this and he breaks it and the crowd laughs yet again. After his act, the crowd starts throwing money at him and Blue Nose approaches the Ringmaster. He is quite pleased with Blue Nose and says if he and Goralina perform, they would make this show a success. Blue Nose gets angered by him, and proceeds to use a whip on him. Thinking that it was part of an act, the audience cheers, laughs, and applauds. Goralina is arrived in chains but Blue Nose helps her to break out and they start running.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are escaped from the circus, but due to the fact that Blue Nose is Jake&amp;rsquo;s tail and was just stretching, its trails were still in the circus, and so the Ringmaster pulls him back. He starts to slap him and one of the ants who was slapping him smeared his hat on his mouth, which changes expression from sad to that of happy. They ask him why is he happy, but he just waits and as soon as the first ray of sunlight strikes him, he begins to undo all his stretching, and finally reaches Jake, who wakes with a snap. Finn notices Jake and says nothing as he does not know it, but the episode ends with Neptr and BMO giggling.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tower (Season 6)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2014/05/season-6-the-tower/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2014/05/season-6-the-tower/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The episode starts with Finn trying to make spaghetti with a bulky candy arm. His bulky arm doesn&amp;rsquo;t help Finn and he starts destroying things and as he continues to mess things up, he gets frustrated and his candy arm explodes. &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Jake&#34;&gt;Jake&lt;/a&gt;comes down stairs, hoping for the spaghetti, but instead sees the mess and tells him that he should just take his time and listen to his &amp;ldquo;Melon Heart.&amp;rdquo; Finn then says he wants to go to space so he can take &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Martin&#34;&gt;his father&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rsquo;s arm. Jake tells him not to do this but to just relax and think and that he&amp;rsquo;s going to the store to buy replacement kitchen supplies for the ones Finn broke. Finn goes outside the tree fort and he lies on the ground. He starts to talk to himself and then suddenly he notices a pile of rocks forming behind him and that there is an odd, sightly transparent arm, where his real arm used to be. He then decides to use this arm to build a tower into space to find his dad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Jake is returning home, the tower has grown considerably and &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Princess_Bubblegum&#34;&gt;Princess Bubblegum&lt;/a&gt; is there and tells Jake that Finn&amp;rsquo;s got a new arm, what she believes to be a telekinetic electro-emotional prosthesis and is dangerous and could hurt him and other people around him. Jake shakes off the notion and says what Finn&amp;rsquo;s doing is healthy and he should just be left alone. As Finn continues his tower he enters the cloud house of a &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Cloud_People&#34;&gt;Cloud person&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Carroll&#34;&gt;She&lt;/a&gt; tells Finn to leave, and when he doesn&amp;rsquo;t, blasts him with lightning with her gun. This moves the house out of the tower and the cloud person then says that Finn must be, &amp;ldquo;One of those swimmers,&amp;rdquo; and leaves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next day large chunks of Ooo&amp;rsquo;s landscape are missing because of the tower, including a rookery of &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Penguins&#34;&gt;penguins&lt;/a&gt;. The cloud person from the day prior returns to Finn, introduces herself as Carroll and apologizes and asks if he&amp;rsquo;s really going to take his father&amp;rsquo;s arm. Finn states that he is and the cloud person talks about how she was water once and how swimmers would always be swimming in her, so she got evaporated and became air. She then tells Finn he should let it go, runaway, and hate his life like she has.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the ground &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/BMO&#34;&gt;BMO&lt;/a&gt; asks Jake what Finn is doing (not before getting crushed into the ground by a falling ice block). Jake says Finn&amp;rsquo;s just working some stuff out and that it&amp;rsquo;s completely healthy, which is directed at PB who is working on some sort of device. PB disagrees and says that Finn could get hurt. As Finn&amp;rsquo;s tower has finally reached the atmosphere, Carroll asks what it&amp;rsquo;s like up there and wonders if she should become space ice. Finn, who is extremely oxygen deprived, sees a similar looking portal to the one the &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Void_Caster&#34;&gt;Void Caster&lt;/a&gt; made in &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Escape_from_the_Citadel&#34;&gt;Escape from the Citadel&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;rdquo; but suddenly a bright light comes at him and he blacks out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finn then wakes up in what seems to be a space ship and walks to the next room to see his &amp;lsquo;father&amp;rsquo; watching TV. Finn surprises his father and punches him into unconsciousness and tries to take his arm. As Martin moans about his favorite arm, Finn changes his mind and it is revealed that Martin was really a disguised PB. She says she tricked Finn and took him to the &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Candy_Kingdom&#34;&gt;Candy Kingdom&lt;/a&gt; fallout bunker, and since he had so little oxygen that he was already hallucinating, the trick was easy to pull off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finn returns home, with his telekinetic arm gone, and tells Jake that he&amp;rsquo;s calmed down. Jake says that&amp;rsquo;s great and asks if Finn wants to do the honors of taking down the tower. Finn says he would and removes a plank of wood near the base of the tower, which then collapses sideways, destroying a large portion of the Candy Kingdom, to the shock of Finn and Jake. The episode ends with Princess Bubblegum screaming, &amp;ldquo;AHHH! MY ARM!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James II (Season 6)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2014/04/season-6-james-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2014/04/season-6-james-ii/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The episode begins with Finn, Jake, and Bubblegum walking and looking for a flower called a Weeping Willy. Once they find it, they start collecting its tears, when Clone James fakes his death claiming that the ground below Bubblegum is loose and performs a fake attempt to save her. He falls into the river and yells, &amp;ldquo;Remember me!&amp;rdquo;. A flashback is shown of the occurrences of the episode &amp;rdquo;&lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/James&#34;&gt;James&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;rdquo; Finn and Jake feel sorry for him, pointing out that it was the 25th time James had sacrificed himself for Bubblegum. Princess Bubblegum then tells them that James faked his death, and points out that the ground near the flower is perfectly solid, and there is no possibility of her falling into the river.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finn and Jake then tell her to bring him back by cloning him, but she tells them that the fake deaths are getting out of hand and it is pointless to award him for his foolish behavior. She says that it&amp;rsquo;s time for him to go into an eternal nap. Finn and Jake protest against her and persuade her to bring him back, but she stands on her ground and declares that there would be no more Jameses. She then tells Finn and Jake to clean up James&amp;rsquo;s apartment to which they reluctantly agree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As they make their way to his apartment, they start talking about his &amp;lsquo;sacrifices&amp;rsquo;, like eating a contaminated cupcake for PB. When they reach the apartment, open the door and switch on the lights they are surprised to find lots of Jameses and ask them who&amp;rsquo;s in charge. A clone James comes forward wearing a lot of medals and introduces himself as James #2. They ask him to explain the scene, to which he replies he was lonely, and wanted more companionship. He knew PB wouldn&amp;rsquo;t make another James, unless he died a hero, so he started faking his death to collect medals, saying that medals make him happy. Jake tells Finn that Princess would be upset about this, to which James #2 gets scared and tells them not to convey this to her. He also tries to bribe them by giving them a medal, but the duo refuse. They say that they won&amp;rsquo;t warn the Princess, because she will eventually find out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finn and Jake go outside and then sit on a bench, laughing at the scene. After some time, they see the Princess whistling and going to James&amp;rsquo; apartment. As soon as Princess enters the building, she shouts, &amp;ldquo;Hey!&amp;rdquo; and all of the Jameses start running out of the house to random places. Finn and Jake enjoy it and laugh. The scene then changes and shows the original James and other Goo Monsters heading out of the pit and towards the kingdom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The scene then returns to the Candy Kingdom, showing Finn and Jake sitting on the walls of the kingdom, and looking below. They see the Princess assembling the Banana Guards and showing them a picture of James. The Banana Guards understand, but as soon as Princess says there are 25 of them, the Banana Guards get all confused and ask questions, such as &amp;ldquo;How can one picture identify all 25?&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Are they brothers?&amp;rdquo; Princess Bubblegum angrily answers their questions. Finn and Jake laugh at their stupidity, when PB notices them and asks for their help. They invite her to their place, and she goes along, while muttering. She arrives at their place, and asks why they are sitting down doing nothing. Jake tells her to sit for 5 minutes and enjoy it. She sits down, and Jake offers her some wall candy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They look below as a Clone James comes to their place. The Banana Guards don&amp;rsquo;t identify him, and even ask him if he has seen the James in the picture. Even Clone James couldn&amp;rsquo;t identify himself which causes the three watching from above to laugh. Eventually, all the Jameses try and cannot identify their own picture. The Banana Guard in charge takes the photo back and asks the name of the first Clone James. He then asks all their names and all of them claim to be &amp;lsquo;James&amp;rsquo;, and say that their names are the same, &amp;ldquo;because they look alike.&amp;rdquo; The Banana Guard then comes to a random conclusion that they are brothers, to which the Jameses reply otherwise. The Banana Guard counts them but the Clone Jameses reassures that there are 25 of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Banana Guard then puts his mental power to work and recalls the orders of PB. He then tells his other guards that they are the guys Princess was talking about.They finally try to capture them while Finn, Jake, and PB laugh at this. The scene then changes to the Banana Guards randomly trying to capture all the Jameses, and in the end, they manage to capture them all. While all this is happening, the Original James and the horde of Goo Monsters arrive at Candy Kingdom, unnoticed. Princess Bubblegum arrives at the place where all Jameses are captured, and snatches their medals, saying they are not heroes. Suddenly, a Gumball Guardian shouts, &amp;ldquo;Evil presence detected!&amp;rdquo; and points to the horde of Goo Monsters. The Banana Guards are then ordered to protect the Candy Kingdom. They obey the order, but since they don&amp;rsquo;t usually fight, some fake their death and one even jabs a spear into his body to fake it. Finn intervenes and uses the spear to attack the Monsters, but on contact with their bodies, the spear melts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finn then warns everyone not to touch them, as anything that touches them melts. The Banana Guards get scared and run into the kingdom. Finn notices some Candy Orphans playing there. He asks Jake for help to bring them inside the kingdom. As they get busy with this task, the Jameses notice PB in danger. They notice the Original James attacking her, and then try to save her by dogpiling on him and fusing together. This causes the Original James to be fused with the clones and be killed. The Jameses say, &amp;ldquo;We told you we were heroes!&amp;rdquo;. Afterwards, Princess Bubblegum awards the medals back to the Jameses. She then gives them a new assignment, which is to &amp;ldquo;go to the wasteland and never come back.&amp;rdquo; The Jameses protest, but Princess Bubblegum interrupts them and tells them she would send them a medal every day. They agree to this and run to the wasteland. The episode ends with Princess Bubblegum saying, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not gonna miss him.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Escape from the Citadel (Season 6)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2014/04/season-6-escape-the-citadel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2014/04/season-6-escape-the-citadel/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Finn&#34;&gt;Finn&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Jake&#34;&gt;Jake&lt;/a&gt; hitch a ride on a Citadel Guardian after he imprisons and transports &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/The_Lich_(character&#34;&gt;The Lich&lt;/a&gt;) to the Citadel. Upon arrival, the Guardian attaches The Lich&amp;rsquo;s crystal prison onto a much larger crystal &amp;ldquo;cell block.&amp;rdquo; Finn then says it is a good riddance for The Lich. As they talk, The Lich begins emitting a gray breath in his cell which the duo don&amp;rsquo;t notice. Finn and Jake then look around for Finn&amp;rsquo;s long-lost father, whom Finn initially suggests might be a Guardian. Jake points out a strange looking &amp;ldquo;old kid&amp;rdquo; who resembles Finn, and it turns out to be Finn&amp;rsquo;s father incarcerated inside a crystal jail cell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finn runs to his dad and looks him closely. A gray slime fire forms on Finn&amp;rsquo;s father&amp;rsquo;s cell, which makes Finn hyper about it and asks Jake about the fire. Jake then points above from where the fire had fallen on the cell. They then notice that the Lich&amp;rsquo;s cell is excreting a gray slime that is beginning to infect the other prisoners and making them under the influence of The Lich. The cell of Finn&amp;rsquo;s father then melts and his father half inside the cell asks Finn for help. Finn uses Jake as flail to break him out of the cell. The Lich&amp;rsquo;s influence over the Citadel enables a massive jailbreak. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finn&amp;rsquo;s father then asks him about the &amp;ldquo;starskipper&amp;rdquo; from which they came, completely ignoring the fact that there is another human in his presence. The prisoners are running amok and attacking the Guardians and making each other gray. After Jake says that Finn is his son, Finn&amp;rsquo;s father is still not surprised by it and starts telling them to find a way to escape. Finn starts to ask his father why he abandoned him, but before he could do, his father jumps in the center of the Citadel, as the ground was melting. Finn again begins to ask him but is cut in middle as a dead guardian pushes them even further. They reach a solid ground and Jake gets frightened by the happenings around him. One of the prisoners is a void caster, who has the power to open portals, so he uses his power to attack a guardian by opening a void in front of a train that &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Starchie&#34;&gt;Starchie&lt;/a&gt; is driving in the &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Candy_Kingdom&#34;&gt;Candy Kingdom&lt;/a&gt;, which crashes into a guardian and kills the guardian. Finn calms Jake down and says to just hijack a floating piece of the Citadel some other Ancients were hijacking and go off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finn&amp;rsquo;s father then tells Jake to smarten up and as he was saying, the last Guardian who was dying shoots a beam that hits Finn&amp;rsquo;s father in the lower right shin, which obliterates all the flesh from a segment of his leg, leaving the bones. Finn starts to panic but his father, who introduces him as &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Martin&#34;&gt;Martin&lt;/a&gt; says that the Guardian&amp;rsquo;s blood has healing properties, and asks Finn to bring it. Finn but puts his question why he was abandoned in the woods, which Martin doesn&amp;rsquo;t remember. He just tells Finn to bring the blood of guardian first. Jake shape-shifts himself into a bridge, enabling Finn to retrieve the regenerative guardian blood and put it on Martin&amp;rsquo;s leg, which is quickly restored to a healthy state. While this is happening, Jake points out to Finn that the Lich came out of the swamp. Finn calls for Martin, who had fled with the other prisoners, abandoning Finn once again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The cell of The Lich bursts and he commands Finn and Jake to fall, which makes them go unconscious. The Lich then entrances Finn, telling him that there is only darkness in his life and only death will be imminent for all life and that he is all alone in the world now. Jake appears unconscious next to Finn. Finn feebly attempts to strike the Lich as he encroaches. His attack was ineffective, but there was some guardian blood near him. The Lich approaches for Finn and as soon as he was to touch, Finn&amp;rsquo;s hand, which was dipped in some guardian blood near him touched the Lich which causes the Lich to scream as flesh begins to grows on his bones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finn then wakes from his trance and throws more guardian blood onto The Lich, restoring more flesh around his chest. Finn then tells Jake to finish him off while he chases after his father. Martin goes to the other prisoners and persuades them to make him their leader, to which they agree. He makes a creature to cut the stem before Finn reaches him. But as soon as the creature cuts the stem, Finn holds the cut end of the stem from both sides. This causes Martin to panic and at Martin&amp;rsquo;s request, the fugitive void caster creates a void to escape into, which begins to suck the floating chunk of land upward faster. Finn grabs the two halves of the severed stem tighter and preventing his father from leaving, telling he won&amp;rsquo;t let him escape and he struggles to hold on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jake tells Finn to let it go, calling Martin a loser but Finn refuses and the &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Grass_Sword&#34;&gt;Grass Sword&lt;/a&gt; takes over Finn&amp;rsquo;s right arm, allowing him one last tremendous pull. Martin grosses out at this and asks the void caster to enlarge the void. This causes much pressure on Finn&amp;rsquo;s hand and at last, Finn&amp;rsquo;s arm gives out and is severed from his body, while Martin states &amp;ldquo;Wait, what about air—&amp;rdquo; right before escaping through the portal. Finn falls into the water below where a small piece of Guardian blood touches his arm, making the stump of an arm sprout a flower. Jake pulls Finn to shore where &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Shelby&#34;&gt;Shelby&lt;/a&gt; is revealed to have been hiding out the entire time. Shelby then sits on Finn&amp;rsquo;s lap while crying. Finn is reminded of the Lich and asks Jake if he finished him off. Jake says there&amp;rsquo;s no need, as the Guardian blood transformed the Lich into a baby-like creature, who is seemingly cute and harmless. Finn, Jake, Shelby, and the infant Lich return to the Candy Kingdom by way of the portal that Starchie drove through during the battle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Later, &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Tree_Trunks_(character&#34;&gt;Tree Trunks&lt;/a&gt;) and &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Mr._Pig&#34;&gt;Mr. Pig&lt;/a&gt; are sitting in her house when outside Finn and Jake&amp;rsquo;s chatter can be heard. The doorbell rings, interrupting a somber Tree Trunks saying, &amp;ldquo;I think we should get a d—.&amp;rdquo; The couple sees outside their door an infant Lich in a stereotypical abandoned-baby basket. Tree Trunks looks excited and implies that this sudden addition to their family has changed her feeling about whatever she was about to say. The infant Lich suddenly says, &amp;ldquo;Hello!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wake Up (Season 6)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2014/04/season-6-wake-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2014/04/season-6-wake-up/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The episode begins with &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Jake&#34;&gt;Jake&lt;/a&gt; partying at Time Room with &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Prismo&#34;&gt;Prismo&lt;/a&gt; and The &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Cosmic_Owl&#34;&gt;Cosmic Owl&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Death&#34;&gt;Death&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Peppermint_Butler&#34;&gt;Peppermint Butler&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Party_God&#34;&gt;Party God&lt;/a&gt;. Jake talks with Prismo after he runs out on nachos and they bump on Peppermint Butler and Death. Peppermint Butler asks Prismo if it is safe for Grob Glob Gob Grod to be taking &amp;ldquo;selfies&amp;rdquo; with an unconscious&lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/The_Lich_(character&#34;&gt;Lich&lt;/a&gt;), to which Prismo replies that ever since he is stuck in the Time Room since his last wish, The Lich had been in a paralyzed state because he could not fulfill his ultimate goal of mass death. Jake then suddenly remembers about Finn, after asking &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Clock_Face&#34;&gt;Clock Face&lt;/a&gt; what time it was and goes to the tree fort after giving a hi-five to Prismo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the tree fort, Jake finds Finn in deep thought and asks Finn about it. Finn tells him that he found out about his human dad being held at a place called The Citadel and began wondering why he left him abandoned in the woods. As they tell about different ideas, Jake tells him to go to Prismo for help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finn and Jake go to Prismo and find Cosmic Owl and Prismo playing Card Wars. Finn and Jake begin to talk to Prismo about the Citadel and after hearing that, the surprised Prismo shows them the conditions of Citadel&amp;rsquo;s prisoners. After some time, Cosmic Owl leaves for some reason. Jake then says that since they had used their wishes he brought &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Shelby&#34;&gt;Shelby&lt;/a&gt; along to make the wish for him, but Shelby wishes for a pony for his girlfriend instead and goes back into Jake&amp;rsquo;s ear from where he came. Prismo tells them the wish could not be useful anyways and explains that you cannot wish yourself into the Citadel. Prismo tells Finn that to gain access to the Citadel, one must commit a &amp;rdquo;cosmic crime,&amp;rdquo; and to do so, all Finn needs to do was to bring a sleeping old man to Prismo&amp;rsquo;s dimension, without waking him up. Prismo gives Finn and Jake pen-lights. Finn and Jake then set out to find the sleeping man which Prismo said was located on a rock that looked like an upside-down duck.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once they reach the rock, Finn and Jake find the old man sleeping in a hut. They take the old man and his bed back to Prismo&amp;rsquo;s dimension, but on the way they accidentally wake him a little and the old man begins emitting strange black beings that can be vanquished by the light of the pen-lights. They vanquish the beings and safely reach the Time Room. Upon arriving, Prismo says to wake the old man and this surprises Finn and Jake, as he said before to not wake him. Prismo then comments that he wanted to see &amp;lsquo;himself&amp;rsquo; before they wake the man up, puzzling Finn and Jake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prismo explains that he is nothing more than the manifestation of a dream being had by the old man. He then says that if the man had woken up, Prismo would cease to exist, and would not be in existence until the man fell back asleep in 1000 years. And also that killing a wish master would be a &amp;ldquo;cosmic crime&amp;rdquo; capable of sending them to the Citadel. Jake did not want to kill his best friend and starts an argument but Prismo persuades him to do so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Suddenly, the Lich springs to life and grabs the old man, waking him. Prismo then says to have changed his plans but disappears before saying anymore. The Lich then observes the Old Man Prismo with fury in his eyes. The old man does not remember any of his dreams, and says he wants to go back home and take a nap, and asks The Lich if he is his son. The Lich was infuriated by Prismo as his wish was not granted, so he blows toxic gas into the old man&amp;rsquo;s nose, turning him into dust. This causes Jake to become enraged at his friend&amp;rsquo;s death. However, before Jake can act, a Citadel Guardian appears from a portal and imprisons the Lich in a crystal cell and starts to take him away, but not before Finn chases after the Lich.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>